小馬鎮，致 Pinkie Pie...
Ponyville to Pinkie Pie...
你突然不見，我們都不知為何
Seems you've left us, and we're all still wond'ring why
小馬鎮，致 Pinkie Pie...
Ponyville to Pinkie Pie...
我們還愛你，別躲起來
We still love you, don't you hide
如你聽得見，你應該知道怎麼辦...
If this reaches you, you'll know just what to do...
這裡是小馬鎮，致 Pinkie Pie
This is Ponyville to Pinkie Pie
只是想要跟你說
just wanted you to know
我們想你，我們只希望你回家
that we miss you, and we wish that you were home
但我們也沒有權力說你的去處
but it's not our place to say where you should go
看來我一直對自己撒謊
Seems that I've been lying to myself
從未如此困難
it's never been so hard
我的蹄子好像帶我走太過
and I think my hooves have taken me too far
我想我該停下，聽聽我的想法
Guess it's time I stopped and listened to my heart
但是，看來我們已陷入了僵局
But here are we sitting at an impasse
困在這月球
Trapped on the moon
火箭已飛走，我們已不在家鄉
Rocketship is gone and I'm not where I belong
雖然我試著說服自己
Though I've tried convincing otherwise
我感到好孤獨
I'm feeling so alone
什麼事都看著好陰沉灰暗
Things aren't looking on the bright side anywhere
要是我有路回家——
If I just had some way home--
——我們帶你走
--we'll take you there
Pinkie Pie, 正是時刻
Pinkie Pie, the time has come
還來得及，你就上來
It's not too late, so just hop on
準備好沒，Pinkie Pie?
Are you ready, Pinkie Pie?
要不要跟，Pinkie Pie?
Are you with us, Pinkie Pie?
聽得見嗎, Pinkie Pie?
Can you hear us, Pinkie Pie?
聽得——
Can you--
現在，看來我們終於能夠回家
Here are we flying home together
跟月球說再見
Last glimpse of the moon
悲劇已趕走，我們已看見家鄉
Tragedy is gone, this is where we all belong